[theme music playing]
[gunshots]
[gun clicks, fires]
[whoosh, slashing sounds]
[machine gun fire]
[machine gun fire continues]
[single gunshot]
[rapid gunfire]
[echoing blast]
[blade whooshing]
[tense music builds]
You should be proud of your daughter
because Emilia shot Raul herself!
Raul was wearing the Jaguar's mask
when she shot him.
[Emilia] I'll kill you both,
Lily and Camia Cruz!
You bastards!
You've killed everyone that I love!
What more do you want?!
[Julio] Raul was never a threat to me!
That's why I never wasted time on him!
I could have killed him just like that.
Just like you. I could get rid of you
at any given time.
Girls. Take Julio with you.
Please handle him with care
because you know how brittle
his bones are.
[Lily] You were the one
guarding my mother.
I'm coming, Mom.
[Helena] What a surprise
to see you, Lily Cruz!
-[gunshot]
-Finally, I get to kill you myself!
-[Helena grunts]
-[thumps]
[Lily] Emilia! Let's meet!
Your mother in exchange for my mother!
Diego. Uncle Damian.
Thank God, you're alive.
Lower your gun.
Emilia and I will trade hostages.
After that, I'll kill this witch myself!
-Is this enough?
-Dig deeper.
Red Dragon wants a deeper grave for him,
so that geezer is closer to hell.
That's enough!
Bury the old man.
Go.
Help them.
[gunshots]
-[Arnaldo] Not so fast.
-[grunts]
-Sorry.
-[gunshot]
She's dead. She's dead.
Wow! Thank you.
Thank you for your loyal service.
[gunshot]
And what about you?
[scoffs] Looks like you had a long day.
Don't worry, I'm here to save you.
Okay.
-Relax.
-[grunts]
[gasps loudly and coughs]
I'm here. I'm here.
Relax, I'm here. I'm here.
Are you good? You okay?
Yeah.
[chuckles]
Now…
Now, where is that witch, Helena Montoya?!
-I am going to kill her!
-[Arnaldo chuckling]
And if she survives, I'll kill her again.
Relax, Grandpa. We'll look for them.
Thank you. Thank you.
[Arnaldo] I got you.
Mom!
-Let Mama go!
-You first!
Let's do this at the same time!
Fine!
[tense music playing]
[tense music intensifies]
It's an ambush!
It's an ambush, baby girl! Shoot them!
-Uncle Damian and--
-Ambush!
Shoot them, baby girl! Shoot them!
-Mama!
-Time to die, Lily Cruz!
[gunshot]
[Lily grunts]
-Mama.
-Lily!
Lily! Lily!
-[gunshots]
[grunts]
[foreboding music]
[Emilia] Mama!
-[rapid gunfire]
-[Camia screaming]
-[Camia] Lily!
-[gunshot]
-[wailing]
-[gunshots]
[rapid gunfire]
[Emilia] Mama!
-[rapid gunfire]
-[Emilia wailing]
[rapid gunfire]
Mama!
[screams]
-[gunshots]
-[man grunts]
-[Camia whimpering]
-Diego!
[Camia whimpering]
[Emilia whimpering]
-[Camia] Lily! Lily!
-[Diego] Lily!
[Camia] Hurry up, Diego! Hurry!
[Emilia whimpering]
Mama!
[Emilia] Be careful.
Please take care of my mama.
-[Helena] Emilia.
-[Emilia] Mama!
Papa!
[Julio] It's all right, Emilia!
Just stay there!
Ronald, stay with my daughter.
Stay there. I'll take care of things here.
[Helena] Julio.
[Damian] Boss.
-[Helena] Julio?
-Yes?
[groaning]
What are you doing here?
I'm here for you.
I am worried about you.
Can't you see that?
-Of course, I worry about you.
-No.
Here I am.
Helena, Helena,
some people just don't and cannot change,
then and until now, just like you,
you're still a fraud.
No, Julio.
I didn't fool you.
You fooled yourself. I loved you.
[Julio] Shh! Shh! Shh!
No matter what you say or do,
it won't change your fate.
This is your destiny.
You know why?
It's because you messed
with the wrong Ardiente.
-You messed with me.
-[clicks tongue]
-Helena, now, don't you worry.
-[Helena sobbing]
Julio, please, no.
[Julio] I want you to know
that I will always love you.
Okay?
[whimpering] No… No.
-[smooches]
-[Helena] No.
Excuse me, please take her
to the hospital.
-I think she's delirious.
-No! No!
She's babbling words.
-[Helena] No! No! No!
-Take care of her!
Make sure she's okay.
-Ronald!
-[Helena] No!
[Julio] Help me.
[Helena] No!
[sighs]
-[Emilia] Papa!
-[Julio] My God.
[Emilia] Papa.
[Julio] Your mom is okay.
She's gonna be okay.
She's just a bit delirious. I don't know.
Maybe because of the medication
that was given to her.
But she'll be all right.
She'll be all right.
Don't worry.
[ambulance siren wailing]
[snivels]
[loud explosion]
Mama!
[wailing]
[Emilia whimpering]
Believe me, Emilia.
Lily Cruz planted a bomb
in your mother's ambulance.
Lily Cruz…
murdered her!
And we're going to avenge Helena.
That's a promise.
[foreboding music playing]
Did you hear that, Mama?
Papa said…
that he'll avenge you.
Because he loves you so much.
And I love you too.
Lily Cruz…
took away the only person
that I loved most.
So now, I am going to kill
all her loved ones.
[foreboding music playing]
[soft dramatic music playing]
Lily.
[weeping]
[whimpering]
Dad…
Dad, I love you so much.
My father did many mistakes.
But he still tried to do the right thing.
I know…
I know it's not enough
to make up for everything
he'd done to you.
But on his behalf,
Lily,
Aunt Camia,
I hope one day…
I hope you can forgive my father.
-[Marlon] Anna, how are they?
-They're safe.
Then why…
Are you okay? What happened?
Anna, are you all right?
I just really need a hug, Marlon.
[soft romantic music playing]
[foreboding music]
-[whimpering]
-Dad! Dad!
Dad! Dad! Dad!
[whimpering]
Dad!
Who did this to you?! Dad! Dad!
Dad! Dad!
Dad!
[Diego] Brother.
Diego!
We need to be strong, brother.
I am here for you.
Thank you.
Thank you, Diego.
I don't know why this happened.
Maybe there's a reason.
Maybe his death will bring us together.
We'll get through this.
-I'm here and I won't leave you.
-[Arnaldo] Thank you.
[whimpers]
[soft dramatic music playing]
[pants]
-You're more beautiful up close.
-Don't touch me!
Sir! Sir! Let me go!
[Raul] I saved your life, Camia.
[Camia] Raul, you already killed me
by locking me up for years!
You are the root
of my family's misfortunes!
Raul, why are you doing this?
Camia, let me make up
for everything I did.
Mom.
[Camia snivels]
We are here to support Diego.
I'm only here for Diego.
Even though Raul is dead,
I still can't forgive him.
I can't forgive him
because he's the root of all this.
The death of my father is his fault.
It's his fault that we got separated.
It's his fault my family was torn apart.
That's why I will never forgive him.
I want to forgive.
I really want to, but…
but I just…
Lily.
He saved me.
Raul saved me, Lily.
Lily…
I want to bury the past,
all my anger and pain towards him.
-I want to forget it all.
-[whimpering]
Someone told me…
that if someone asks for forgiveness,
especially if that person is sincere
we should forgive him with our hearts.
Not just for their sake,
but for us to heal as well.
I am also grateful to Raul.
Because…
he tried to correct his past mistakes.
So, we should learn to forgive.
At least, it eases the pain
of what he did to your father
and to our family.
Lily.
[soft dramatic music playing]
[Anna] Isn't it obvious?!
Jepoy, I like you. I like you.
I really like you, Anna!
You're always in my head and in my heart!
Is there still a room for me in there?
[Anna] You're always in my heart, Jepoy.
-Don't leave my side.
-I won't.
-[Jepoy] Promise?
-[Anna] Promise.
Jepoy.
[Jepoy] I didn't mean to.
I didn't mean to.
[Anna] You didn't mean to?!
You didn't mean to fool around
and hurt me, Jepoy?!
[Jepoy] I will never love anyone
the way that I love you, Anna.
[engine revs]
[handbrake squeaks]
-[phone dialing]
-[hangs up]
Why aren't you answering, Madrigal?!
-[phone dialing]
-[hangs up]
[scoffs]
Why aren't you answering?!
[Natalie] Oh, Madrigal.
Why am I worried about you?
You know, I've had a lot of men
for a lot of reasons.
All of them ended up leaving me.
I don't care if they burn in hell.
But you, Madrigal,
I don't want anything bad
to happen to you.
You're different.
I want you to choose me.
And I've never wanted anyone
as much as I want you.
[handbrake squeaks]
[soft dramatic music playing]
[Damian] I learned to love because of you.
I want to be a good person because of you.
[Camia] Jay, we should install
cameras here,
so we can monitor the front gate.
We should put one in the corner too.
Relay it to the security personnel.
[Damian] You deserve
someone better than me.
Am I worthy of you?
[Camia] Do we have cameras in that area?
Yeah, I think we're good.
Damian.
It's good that you've moved
to a new house.
We need to leave the old house,
so we could bury its tragic memories.
I just want to assure your safety.
Damian, we're safe because of you,
also to Diego and Raul.
I will be forever grateful to you three.
But Damian,
you need to own up to your mistakes.
I know.
I'm turning myself in.
I will pay for all my crimes,
so I can be worthy of your love.
[soft dramatic music playing]
I hope this isn't the last time
that we can be together.
I hope…
I hope you can wait for me, Camia.
Damian.
I'll wait for you.
I'll wait for you, Damian.
-Does it hurt?
-Not much.
[romantic music playing]
Life comes so fast.
Just recently…
I lost Auntie and Uncle.
And now, I lost Dad.
It's scary.
You never know when your time will come.
I know I haven't really shown you
how much I love you.
But that will never happen again.
I'll show you every single day, Diego,
how much I love you.
We can't afford to surrender.
But whenever I think about the danger,
the revenge of the Ardientes,
will we ever find peace?
When will this end?
-Lily, what if we don't make--
-[Lily] We'll make it through.
We have a future, Diego.
My love for you, your love for me,
and our love for each other
will give us strength and hope
for a brighter future.
I love you.
I love you too.
[soft romantic music playing]
[Jepoy] My goodness.
What are you doing here?
Where have you been?!
I've been calling you,
but you weren't picking up.
Why?!
Lily went missing.
The Ardientes kidnapped her,
so I was busy tracking them.
-Not now, I'm tired.
-Wow!
Well, you could have answered
my call and told me that.
[Jepoy] And why do I need to inform you?
Because I'm your boss
and you are my henchman.
I should know where you are
every single time.
[Jepoy] Yeah, you're my boss
and I'm your henchman.
But I'm not your puppet. And besides…
Well, I own you. Have you forgotten?
What's with me?!
Why do you keep bothering me?!
What's with me, huh?!
-Do you really wanna know?!
-Yeah! Tell me!
I love you!
[scoffs]
[whimpers]
I love you, Jepoy!
-I love you, Madrigal!
-Ma'am.
How many times do I have to…
[Natalie whimpers]
I thought, I could never love like this.
But you're different.
You're different.
And when I'm with you,
I feel so safe.
I love you.
[Natalie] I love you…
so much.
Please love me too.
[foreboding music playing]
[sighs]
Oh, how I loved you, Helena.
How I loved you.
But love makes people weak!
And I must never be weak.
And you of all people should know that.
You went too far.
You and Grandma could have been
a power couple.
It's just too bad,
the dragon played with fire
and she got burned.
Traitors pay a steep price!
How's Mom?
She's a big girl.
Your mom is a very strong woman.
[sighs] She'll get through this.
She'll soon forget…
the deaths of your father and grandmother.
One thing is for sure,
she'll never suspect…
that I killed her mother.
You know what's funny?
We abducted Lily and Camia Cruz,
toyed with them, and tried to kill them,
but in the end,
we're the ones who lost lives.
I mean, come on, you must admit,
we got a taste of karma.
No, my son.
The death of your grandmother
is what you call a blessing in disguise.
Now that she's dead,
even if her ghost haunts us,
she won't be able to stop us
from claiming her wealth.
So, what belongs to her,
now completely belongs to us.
-[Emilia] Mama.
-[Helena] Emilia, my daughter.
[Emilia] I've waited all these years.
[Helena] Not longer
than I've waited, Emilia.
[Emilia] Are these all mine?!
[Helena] I'll get you the crown back.
You will be the queen of Ardiente!
I would like to introduce to you
my long-lost daughter,
Emilia Ardiente-Torillo!
[Arnaldo] Dad was not perfect.
Nobody is perfect.
But he tried his best to be a father to me
and to my brother.
We loved him as our father.
Dad, your dream finally came true.
The two of us have reconciled as brothers.
We love you very much.
Yes, Dad. We love you so much.
We'll see you in heaven.
[soft dramatic music playing]
[soft dramatic music continues playing]
[Emilia] Step aside! Stop!
I'll bury my husband myself!
Fine! Accompany his grave!
[people yelling]
[Julio] Lily Cruz is the real Red Dragon!
She is the real criminal!
[Damian] Don't believe Julio Ardiente.
I am the Jaguar.
I used to work for Red Dragon.
I know the entire truth.
[Arnaldo] It's time to create
a new nightmare for them.
Julio had something to do
with Helena's death.
Now, the question is, who is helping him?
[theme music playing]